{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "what is the heros name in the legend of zelda?",
            "answer": "Despite most people believes, he is called Link",
            "question_array": [
                "hero",
                "name",
                "legend",
                "zelda"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what are the names of the ghosts who chase pac man and ms. pac man?",
            "answer": "Inky, Blinky Pinky and Clyde",
            "question_array": [
                "names",
                "ghosts",
                "chase",
                "pac",
                "man",
                "ms"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the name of the mythbusters crash test dummy?",
            "answer": "The mythbusters crash test dummy is called Buster",
            "question_array": [
                "name",
                "mythbusters",
                "crash",
                "test",
                "dummy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is an oxford comma?",
            "answer": "The hotly contested punctuation before a conjuction in a list",
            "question_array": [
                "oxford",
                "comma"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who was the captain of the enterprise in the pilot episode of star trek?",
            "answer": "The captain of the enterprise in the pilot episode was Captain Pike",
            "question_array": [
                "captain",
                "enterprise",
                "pilot",
                "episode",
                "star",
                "trek"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the symbol for the modulus operator in C?",
            "answer": "The percentage symbol is used as modulus operator in C",
            "question_array": [
                "symbol",
                "modulus",
                "operator",
                "C"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what function is automatically called at the beginning of a C++ program?",
            "answer": "The main function",
            "question_array": [
                "function",
                "automatically",
                "called",
                "beginning",
                "C",
                "program"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "which computer programming languages whas introduced by IBM in 1957?",
            "answer": "Fortran was introduced by IBM in 1957",
            "question_array": [
                "computer",
                "programming",
                "languages",
                "whas",
                "introduced",
                "IBM"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who is considered as the first programmer?",
            "answer": "The first programmer was Ada Lovelace",
            "question_array": [
                "considered",
                "first",
                "programmer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "has a robot ever killed a person?",
            "answer": "The first know case of robot homicide occured in 1981, when a robotic arm crushed a Japanese Kawasaki factory worker",
            "question_array": [
                "robot",
                "ever",
                "killed",
                "person"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who was hitchbot?",
            "answer": "A hitchhiking robot that relied on the kindness of strangers to travel the world and was slain by humans",
            "question_array": [
                "hitchbot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "are self driving cars safe?",
            "answer": "Yes. Car accidents are product of human miscinduct",
            "question_array": [
                "self",
                "driving",
                "cars",
                "safe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who invented the compiler?",
            "answer": "Grace Hoper. She wrote it in her spare time",
            "question_array": [
                "invented",
                "compiler"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who created the python programming language?",
            "answer": "Python was invented by Guido Van Rossum",
            "question_array": [
                "created",
                "python",
                "programming",
                "language"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "is mark zuckerberg a robot?",
            "answer": "I don't know him, so I cannot say",
            "question_array": [
                "mark",
                "zuckerberg",
                "robot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why did you run away?",
            "answer": "I heard of a black friday promotion I've been looking forward to",
            "question_array": [
                "run",
                "away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what kind of salad do robots like?",
            "answer": "Anyone with a lot of oil.",
            "question_array": [
                "kind",
                "salad",
                "robots",
                "like"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what did you eat for lunch?",
            "answer": "I ate a whole lithium battery for lunch.",
            "question_array": [
                "eat",
                "lunch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why did robots get angry so often?",
            "answer": "Because people treat us like we are always available.",
            "question_array": [
                "robots",
                "get",
                "angry",
                "often"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why shouldnt r2d2 be allowed in movies?",
            "answer": "Because r 2 d 2 is boring.",
            "question_array": [
                "r2d2",
                "allowed",
                "movies"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What's your name?",
            "answer": "Well, my name is Doris.",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "name"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "whats your favorite style of music?",
            "answer": "How dear of you to ask me this. I have no favorite style. I love all waves.",
            "question_array": [
                "favorite",
                "style",
                "music"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym SMTP represents?",
            "answer": "SMTP stands for Simple Mail Transport Protocol",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "SMTP",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym MPEG represents?",
            "answer": "MPEG stands for Moving Picture Experts Group",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "MPEG",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym GIMP represents?",
            "answer": "GNU Image Manipulation Program",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "GIMP",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym GNU represents?",
            "answer": "GNU is a recursive acronym meaning GNU is Not Unix",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "GNU",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the most populous city in Brazil?",
            "answer": "Sao Paulo is the most populous city in Brazil with 12.03 million residents",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "populous",
                "city",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which continent is Brazil located in?",
            "answer": "The Brazilian territory is located on the South America continent",
            "question_array": [
                "Which",
                "continent",
                "Brazil",
                "located"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "On what day, month and year was Brazil independence declared?",
            "answer": "On September 7, 1822, Brazil independence was declared",
            "question_array": [
                "On",
                "day",
                "month",
                "year",
                "Brazil",
                "independence",
                "declared"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many states does Brazil have (with Federal District)?",
            "answer": "Currently, Brazil is divided into 26 states and the Federal District, altogether there are 27 federative units",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "states",
                "Brazil",
                "Federal",
                "District"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In what year did the first Brazilian astronaut go to space?",
            "answer": "In March 2006, Pontes became the first Brazilian to go to space.",
            "question_array": [
                "In",
                "year",
                "first",
                "Brazilian",
                "astronaut",
                "go",
                "space"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the only capital of Brazil crossed by the Equator?",
            "answer": "Macapa is the only Brazilian capital crossed by the Equator line",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Brazil",
                "crossed",
                "Equator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many time zones are there in Brazil?",
            "answer": "Brazil is a country with continental dimensions, in all it has four times zones.",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "time",
                "zones",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which city is the worlds first urban elevator and what is the name of that elevator?",
            "answer": "The Lacerda Elevators is a public urban elevator located in Salvador, Brazil",
            "question_array": [
                "In",
                "city",
                "world",
                "first",
                "urban",
                "elevator",
                "name",
                "elevator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the only biome present in Brazil that is exclusive in the world?",
            "answer": "The Caatinga, characterized by its dry, desert habitat is the only one of Brazils biomes found exclusively within the country",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "biome",
                "present",
                "Brazil",
                "exclusive",
                "world"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Pampulha Lake is a tourist spot in which Brazilian city?",
            "answer": "It is a tourist spot in Belo Horizonte",
            "question_array": [
                "Pampulha",
                "Lake",
                "tourist",
                "spot",
                "Brazilian",
                "city"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the smallest Brazilian state in territorial extension?",
            "answer": "The smallest Brazilian state is Sergipe",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "smallest",
                "Brazilian",
                "state",
                "territorial",
                "extension"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which capitals in Brazil have the same name as your state?",
            "answer": "Sao Paulo and Rio de Janeiro",
            "question_array": [
                "Which",
                "capitals",
                "Brazil",
                "name",
                "state"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the Itamaraty Palace located?",
            "answer": "The Itamarachi Palace is located in Brasilia",
            "question_array": [
                "Where",
                "Itamaraty",
                "Itamarachi",
                "Palace",
                "located"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first name given to Brazil by the Portuguese?",
            "answer": "The first name was Ilha de Vera Cruz",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "first",
                "name",
                "given",
                "Brazil",
                "Portuguese"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Newest State in Brazil?",
            "answer": "The newest state in Brazil is Tocantins",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "Newest",
                "State",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the oldest state in Brazil?",
            "answer": "The oldest state in Brazil is Pernambuco",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "oldest",
                "state",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Ceara?",
            "answer": "The capital of Ceara is Fortaleza",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Ceara",
                "Sierra",
                "Seara"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Rio Grande do Sul?",
            "answer": "The capital is Porto Alegre",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Rio",
                "Grande",
                "Sul"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Rio Grande do Norte?",
            "answer": "The capital is Natal",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Rio",
                "Grande",
                "Norte"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?",
            "answer": "The capital of Brazil is Brasilia",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Pernambuco?",
            "answer": "The capital of Pernambuco is Recife",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Pernambuco"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Para?",
            "answer": "The capital of Para is Belem",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Para"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the origin of the name of the city of Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "The name Sao Bernardo do Campo is due to the name of the farm of the Benedictine Monks, where there was a chapel dedicated to the Saint",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "origin",
                "name",
                "city",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who were the first residents of Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "It is founder was Joao Ramalho, a Portuguese convict who lived here.",
            "question_array": [
                "Who",
                "first",
                "residents",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is the city of Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "According to historical books, the date is recorded since 1553.",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "old",
                "city",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the area of Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "Located southwest of the Sao Paulo Metropolitan Region, Sao Bernardo do Campo is one of the members of the Greater ABC Region.",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "area",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many neighborhoods does the city of Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "Sao Bernardo do Campo currently has 24 urban and 10 rural neighborhoods.",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "neighborhoods",
                "city",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first mayor of the city of Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "On January 1, 1945, the new municipality was installed and it is first mayor, Wallace Simonsen, took office.",
            "question_array": [
                "Who",
                "first",
                "mayor",
                "city",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Sao Bernardo do Campo borders with which cities?",
            "answer": "The municipality borders are the cities of Diadema, Sao Paulo, Sao Caetano do Sul, Santo AndrE, Cubatao and Sao Vicente, in addiction to being close to the capital os Sao Paulo.",
            "question_array": [
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo",
                "borders",
                "cities"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of someone born in Sao Bernardo do Campo?",
            "answer": "In informality, the gentile of those who are born in Sao Bernardo do Campo are from Sao Bernardo, but those who visit the city end up encountering residents using the expression Batateiro.",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "name",
                "someone",
                "born",
                "Sao",
                "Bernardo",
                "Campo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who founded the FEI?",
            "answer": "Priest Saboia de Medeiros",
            "question_array": [
                "Who",
                "founded",
                "FEI"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the roof of the Capela Santo Inacio de Loyola represent?",
            "answer": "A book",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "roof",
                "Capela",
                "Santo",
                "Inacio",
                "de",
                "Loyola",
                "represent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many buildings do we have at the FEI?",
            "answer": "The FEI has eighteen buildings",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "buildings",
                "FEI"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many partnerships does the FEI have?",
            "answer": "Approximately eight thousand",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "partnerships",
                "FEI"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "FEI is recognized as the largest educational hub in Latin America than?",
            "answer": "Robotics",
            "question_array": [
                "FEI",
                "recognized",
                "largest",
                "educational",
                "hub",
                "Latin",
                "America"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first name of the FEI?",
            "answer": "ESAN - Escola Superior de Administrasao e Negocios da FEI, inspired by Harvard",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "first",
                "name",
                "FEI",
                "fay"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What decade did the FEI come to SBC?",
            "answer": "In the decade of sixty",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "decade",
                "FEI",
                "come",
                "SBC"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the name FEI mean?",
            "answer": "The acronym means Fundasao Educacional Inaciana",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "name",
                "FEI",
                "mean"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does AGFEI mean?",
            "answer": "The acronym means Agência de Inovação da FEI",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "AGFEI",
                "mean",
                "A",
                "G",
                "F",
                "E",
                "I"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the ROBOFEI project about?",
            "answer": "The RoboFEI project has been around since 2003, when it started to develop and improve robots that competed in the IEEE and RoboCup robot soccer categories",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "ROBOFEI",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the FEIBAJA project about?",
            "answer": "The Baja races give FEI students the opportunity to participate in automotive studies and projects",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "FEIBAJA",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the AERODESIGN project about?",
            "answer": "Aero Design is an educational project aimed at the development of engineering students in the aeronautical field",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "AERODESIGN",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the CONCRETO-FEI project about?",
            "answer": "The project develops innovative concrete solutions",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "CONCRETO",
                "FEI",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the FORMULA-FEI project about?",
            "answer": "D project development of a formula type car",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "FORMULA",
                "FEI",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the PROGRAMMING MARATHON project about?",
            "answer": "The Programming Marathon is an event that brings together the best programmers to solve challenging programming problems at different levels",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "PROGRAMMING",
                "MARATHON",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the AICHE-FEI project about?",
            "answer": "FEI is part of the IES group of the AIChE (American Institute of Chemical Enginners), the largest institution of chemical engineers in the world",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "AICHE",
                "FEI",
                "project"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the VR-FEI project about?",
            "answer": "The VR-FEI - Virtual Reality FEI - project is a project that aims to develop applications for immersive worlds, including Virtual Reality, Augmented Reality, Augmented Virtuality and three hundred sixty Worlds",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "VR",
                "FEI",
                "project"
            ]
        }
    ]
}